(Raj:)Look, we admit it.
(Raj:)The idea that you guys came
up with was really good,
(Raj:)and I'd love
your help.
(Howard:)I suppose it couldn't have been
easy for you to say that.
(Raj:)It wasn't, so...
are you in?
(Sheldon:)Certainly.
Sure.
Great.
(Leonard:)Now that we're all
on the same page,
(Leonard:)let's get together tonight
and work on it.
"Get together tonight"?
(Sheldon:)Leonard, stop trying
to control everything,
(Sheldon:)and give poor Raj a chance to
come up with what we should do.
(Sheldon:)Go ahead, Raj.
(Raj:)Okay, I think
we should do it right now.
(Sheldon:)Tonight works better for me.
(Leonard:)Okay.
(sighs)
Okay, it's just an audition.
Why am I nervous?
Maybe it's a good thing.
Just means I want it.
And I can have it.
This feels right.
Why did I ever give this up?
(Penny(voiceover):)I'm starting to remember.